- 咖啡来了   -  谢谢
- Here you go.         - Thank you.
"瑞秋
"Say, Rachel...
不知道你有空时 要不要跟我去看电影
...I was wondering if you'd like to go to a movie with me sometime...
当我的情人"
...as my lover."
太直接了
Mm. Too out there.
"或许你有空时可以跟我去吃点东西
"Maybe you'd just like to get something to eat with me sometime...
当我的情人"
...as my lover."
- 嗨   -  嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
好吧 我们该去血拼了
All right, let's go shopping.
在我们出发前 我有事要跟你说
You know, before we go, uh, there's something I need to say.
- 好吧   -  好吧
- Oh. Okay.     - Okay.
我一直都在暗恋着你
I've kind of had this, uh... This crush on you.
因为那时你跟罗斯在一起 我什么事都不能做
But since you were with Ross, I didn't do anything about it.
现在你们分手了 我真的很想约你出去
Now that you're not, I'd really like to ask you out sometime.
那是我现在正要做的事
So that's what I'm doing now.
我掉了一个杯子
I dropped a cup.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
所以在几年内语音辨识系统
So that's why within a few years, that voice recognition...
会成为标准电脑配备
...is gonna be pretty much standard on any computer.
你就可以这么说 "帮我洗车 打扫房间"
You know, so you could be, like, "Wash my car. Clean my room."
虽然它无法做那些事
It's not gonna be able to do any of those things...
但它会了解你说的每一句话
...but it'll understand what you're saying.
- 这真的很棒   -  没错
- Oh, this was so great.     - Yeah, it was.
好吧
All right, then.
再见
Bye.
不住在这里的人们 你们好
Hello, people who do not live here.
- 嗨   -  哈罗
- Hi.     - Hello.
我给你们钥匙是为了不时之需
I gave you a key for emergencies.
我们的玉米片吃完了
We were out of Doritos.
你跟百万富翁约会得如何
Hey, how'd the date go with Mr. Millionaire?
百万富翁先生刚刚恢复单身生活
"Mr. Millionaire. New, from Snooty Playthings.
跟第三任太太分道扬镖
Third wife sold separately."
他真的很棒 我们在一起很开心
He's great. I mean, we have such a good time together.
他既风趣有可爱 我却一点都不喜欢他
He's so funny and so sweet. And I'm not attracted to him at all.
- 真的吗   -  对
- Still?     - No.
这把我逼疯了 在各方面他都是完美男人
It's driving me crazy. I mean, in every other way, he's like the perfect guy.
他什么都有 他真的什么都有
He has everything. Plus, he actually has everything.
原厂出品的真人大小 星际大战帝国风暴突击队装备
Life-sized lmperial Storm Troopers from Sharper lmage?
他有两套
Two.
我跟乔伊可以穿上它们打一架吗
Wow. Can Joey and I put them on and fight?
妈妈 爸爸 我是坏男孩
Oh, Mommy. Oh, Daddy. I am a big old baddy.
我想他应该是被录取了
I guess he must've gotten the part in that play.
或是葛洛丽雅•伊斯特芬说对了
Either that or Gloria Estefan was right.
最后 节奏会让你上了瘾
Eventually, the rhythm is going to get you.
（路西尔洛泰剧场）
- 乔伊 还好吗   -  我很好
- Joe, how's it going?     - Good.
- 嗨   -  嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
你演安德丽娜
Ah, so you're playing Adrianne, huh?
对 你是白痴表弟吗
Yes. Are you one of the retarded cousins?
不 我演你的丈夫维多 我是乔伊•崔比亚尼
No, no. Uh, I'm playing your husband, Victor. I'm Joey Tribbiani.
幸会 凯特•米勒
Hi. Nice to meet you. Kate Miller.
这出戏很不错吧
Heh. So the, uh, play's pretty great, huh?
对 我喜欢珍妮佛•班伯利的作品
Oh, yeah. I love Jennifer Banberry's work.
她非常尖锐地
She's so brilliantly incisive...
剖析中产阶级心态
...when it comes to deconstructing the psyche of the middle class.
算了吧 她超棒的
Oh, forget about it. She rocks. Ha, ha.
我们见过面吗
Where do I know you from?
德瑞克•雷莫瑞医生
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
"我们的日子"
Days of our Lives?
被"青春节奏"票选为最想交往的外科医生
Voted most datable neurosurgeon by Teen Beat?
不 不是那样的
No, that's not it.
你是肥皂剧演员
So you're a soap actor.
能演出真正的戏剧 你一定非常兴奋
Well, this must be exciting for you, being in a real play. Hmm?
我演过戏 我是认真的演员
Hey, I've done plays before. I'm a serious actor.
是那部广告
That infomercial.
牛奶洒出来的广告
For the milk-carton-spout thing.
你是不会倒牛奶的那个家伙
You're the guy who doesn't know how to pour milk.
我会倒牛奶 但我让你相信我不会
See, I actually can pour milk. But I got you believing that I couldn't.
看吧 那才是演技
Ha, ha. Now, see, that's acting.
对 最后你被饼干噎到
Right. At the end, you choked on a cookie.
对 那是真的
Yeah, that was real.
- 我不敢相信马克会约你出去   -  我知道
- Wow. I cannot believe Mark asked you out.     - I know.
你打算怎么跟他说
Well, So, what are you gonna tell him?
我跟他说我会考虑 但我要拒绝他
Well, I told him I would think about it, but I'm gonna tell him no.
我现在我不想跟任何人约会
I mean, I think I'd say no to anybody right now.
那真的很奇怪 我站在那里
Oh, but it was so strange. I mean, I'm standing there...
那个迷人可爱的男人要跟我约会
...with this charming, cute guy who's asking me to go out with him...
我可以那么做
...which I'm allowed to do...
可是我觉得有罪恶感 就像是我背叛了罗斯
...and I felt guilty, you know, like I'd be cheating on Ross or something.
好吧 或许那表示
Wow. So, okay, maybe that means...
你还没有忘记罗斯 还有你跟你爸之间有问题
...that you're not over Ross yet and you have issues with your father.
我跟我爸没问题
I don't have any issues with my father.
好吧 或许那只是罗斯的关系
Okay, so it's probably just the Ross thing.
我讨厌这个女人 我恨她
I hate this woman. I hate her.
她跟剧团里的人说广告的事
She told everyone in the company about that infomercial...
现在他们老找我帮他们打开饮料罐
...and now they all keep asking me to open their drinks.
好吗 每次我办不到时 他们都会嘲笑我
Okay? And whenever I can't do it, they're all, like, laughing at me.
- 哈罗   -  嘿
- Hello.     - Hey.
瑞秋打电话给我
So Rachel called.
她想见我
Wants to see me.
等一下我就要过去
Going over in a minute.
- 你觉得她想谈什么吗   -  或许她终于冷静下来
- Wow. What do you think she wants?     - Well, maybe the crazy fog has lifted...
了解到没有我的生活…
...and she realizes that life without me...
太逊了
...sucks.
有可能 你非常可爱 如果我跟你分手 我也会想你
It's possible. You are very lovable. I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
我只是想支持你
Just trying to be supportive.
像个男子汉来支持我吧
Well, be supportive like a guy.
如果我跟你分手 我也会想你
If I broke up with you, I'd miss you.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
你找我
You, uh, wanted to see me?
对
Yeah.
这箱是你的东西
Uh, here's a box of your stuff.
- 什么   -  里面是帽子 衬衫跟光碟
- What?     - Uh, it's just like hats and a shirt and CD's.
你留在这里的东西
Just sort of stuff that you've left here.
你在做什么 你想伤害我吗
What are you doing? Are you trying to hurt me or something?
罗斯
Ross.
看起来我们都该有新生活了
It just seems that, you know, it's time we, you know, move on.
你不那么认为吗
I mean, don't you think?
- 对   - 对
- Yes.     - Yeah.
- 对 我是那么想的   -  太好了
- Yes, I do.     - Good.
我真的是那么想的
Yeah, I really do.
嘿
Hey...
这是礼物耶
This was a gift.
罗斯 那是你从博物馆礼品店免费拿回来的
Ross, you got that for free from the museum gift shop.
它还是礼物
It's still a gift.
我从礼品店拿回来的
I got it from the gift shop.
好吧 马克杯给我 我可以留下马克杯
Okay. All right. Give me the mug. I'll keep the mug.
不 别可怜我 事实上…
No. You know, don't do me any favors. In fact, where...
我其他的东西在哪里 譬如我的…
Where's the rest of my stuff? Huh? Like my, um...
这本书是我的
Hey. This book is mine.
还有你穿着睡觉的汗衫呢 我要把它拿回来 没错
And that T-shirt you sleep in? I'd like that back too. Yes, I do.
你知道我多爱那件汗衫 你从来不穿那件汗衫
You know how much I love that T-shirt. You never even wear that T-shirt.
我只是想帮助你追寻新生活
I'm just trying to help you move on.
你真是个小气的家伙
Oh, you are a petty man.
你是个小气…
You are a petty, petty...
- 小气   -  小气
- Petty...     - ...petty, petty...
- 小心眼   -  小心眼
- ...small...      - ...small...
你是不爽才会这么做
You are so just doing this out of spite.
不…
Uh-uh. No, no, no.
我要一直穿着它 我喜欢这件汗衫
I'm gonna wear this all the time. I love this shirt.
你15岁后就没穿过它 你根本就穿不下了
You haven't worn that since you were 15. It doesn't even fit you anymore.
- 对   - 对
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.     - Yeah, yeah.
好吧
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
（法兰克说放轻松）
如果你不介意的话 我要拿着我的东西…
Now, if you don't mind, I'm gonna take the rest of my stuff...
去放轻松了
...and relax...
穿着我最喜欢的汗衫
...in my favorite shirt.
祝你有个愉快的夜晚
You have a pleasant evening.
你是亿万富翁
So you're, like, a zillionaire.
你的年纪跟我们一样大
And you're our age. You're our age.
你知道吗 你该买下一个州
You know what? You should, like, buy a state...
把州名改成你的名字
...and then just name it after yourself.
什么 譬如说彼特•达科塔
What, like, "Pete Dakota"?
或是密西西比•彼特
Or "Mississi-Pete."
我知道了 彼特•芝加哥
Ooh, ooh, I got it: "Pete Chicago."
芝加哥不是一个州 乔伊
That's not a state, Joe.
密西西比•彼特就是吗
Oh, and "Mississi-Pete" is?
我得走了 后会有期
I gotta go, so, uh, I'll see you guys later.
- 好吧 你的年纪跟我们一样大   -  好的
- Okay. You're our age.     - Okay.
明天见面
So, uh, are we on for tomorrow?
当然
Absolutely.
快走吧
Now get out of here, you.
好吧 我该摸的地方都摸过了
Okay, I'm running out of places I can touch him.
我有毛病吗
Is there something wrong with me?
为什么我只喜欢跟我没有未来的男人
I mean, why am I only attracted to guys where there's no future?
他们不是太老 就是太年轻
Either they're too old or they're too young.
彼特为我疯狂
And there's Pete, who's crazy about me...
他是那么完美 我对他是手到擒来
...and he's absolutely perfect, and there's, like, zip going on.
说真的 我真的有毛病吗
Seriously. Does it sound like something's wrong with me?
对 应该是吧
Yeah, kind of.
开心 我该那么做吗 维多
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be, Vic?
开心
Happy?
你何不告诉我你想怎么做
Well, why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be? Huh?
因为我就是搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out.
我跟你说话 你没反应
I talk to you, and nothing.
你看着我 完全没反应
You look at me, and it's nothing.
就是没反应
Nothing.
太好了
Tasty.
我真的开始觉得你们有一段情 太棒了
I'm really starting to feel like you guys have a history. It's nice.
- 我对这场戏有个问题   -  请说
- I have a question about this scene.     - Yes.
我不了解 为什么安德丽娜会喜欢维多
Well, I don't understand why Adrianne's attracted to Victor.
要抽丝剥茧
Peel the onion.
首先他长得很帅
First of all, he's good-looking.
我想我的角色还需要其他的理由
I think my character is gonna need a bit more of a reason than that.
这个理由可以吗 剧本是那么写的
Oh, hey, how about this one? Uh, it says so in the script.
我也不知道为什么我的角色会喜欢你
You know, I don't know why my character likes you either.
剧本上写着你是个贱人
I mean, it says in the script here that you're a bitch.
- 剧本才没有那么写   - 我的剧本就是那么写的
- It doesn't say that in the script.     - It does in mine.
我可以把它吹干 或是涂发胶 那一点都不重要
I can blow-dry it, I can put gel on it. It doesn't matter.
中间那个部分
I still wind up with this little cowlick-y thing...
还是翘了起来 真的很讨厌
...on the middle part of my head. It's so annoying.
- 你觉得困扰吗   -  是你让我觉得困扰
- Does it bug you?     - You bug me.
你有可能没看到这一幕吗
Is there any chance you didn't see that?
罗斯 别再那么做了
Ross, you gotta stop, okay?
你不能连续盯着窥视孔三小时
You can't just stare through the peephole for three hours.
你的眼睛会坏掉的
You're gonna get peep-eye.
我就知道 我一直都知道她喜欢他
I knew it. I knew it. I always knew she liked him.
她可以拒绝的 看看她做了什么
She'd say no, but here we are, right?
我们才刚分手 她马上就跟他约会
We just broke up, first thing she does.
你们不是才刚分手
You didn't just break up.
才三星期而已
Hey, it's been, like, three weeks.
你在以为你们分手后三小时就跑去跟别人上床
You slept with somebody three hours after you thought you broke up.
子弹飞出去的速度都没那么快
I mean, bullets have left guns slower.
他们回来了
Here they come. Here they... Oh.
如果她跟他吻别 我发誓我要自杀
If she kisses him good night, I'm gonna kill myself. I swear.
我看不下去了
I can't watch.
快点 约会结束了
Come on. Date over. Date over.
- 太好了 她要进去了   -  好的
- Here we go. She's going in.     - Okay.
她要进去了 等一下 他也进去了
She's going in. Ha, ha. Wait. He's going in.
他要进去了
He's going in.
门关上了 门关着我看不到
The door's closed. I can't see anything with the door closed.
发明门的人可以安息了
And the inventor of the door rests happily in his grave.
好吧 我得想想办法 我必须阻止他们
Okay, I have to do something. I mean, I have to stop it.
- 阻止他们做什么   -  我不知道
- Stop what?     - I don't know.
但直觉跟我说换作是我 我们会做什么
But I have a feeling that my being there will do it.
我要过去借东西
I'll go over and I will borrow something.
- 果汁 我需要果汁   -  不
- Juice. I need juice.     - No.
- 不可以   -  帮帮我
- You can't.     - A little help.
- 我得阻止他们   -  我是你的朋友
- They must be stopped.     - I am your friend...
我不能让你这么做
...and I am not gonna let you do this.
你真的好壮
You are surprisingly strong.
- 我需要果汁 人们需要果汁   -  听着
- I need juice. People need juice.     - Look, man...
- 人们需要果汁 他们需要…   -  听我说
- People need juice. Juice. They need...     - Listen to me.
她展开新生活了 就算不是他 也会是别人
She's moving on, okay? If it's not this guy, it's gonna be somebody else.
如果你考虑租用我的窥视孔
And unless you're thinking about subletting my peephole...
你得接受事实 你们结束了
...you are gonna have to get used to the fact that the relationship is over.
好吗 你们结束了
Okay, man? It's over.
- 对 好吧   -  好吧
- Yeah, okay.     - Okay.
我真的很想她
It's just I miss her so much.
我知道
I know.
为什么你们的马克杯底写着编号
Why do all your coffee mugs have numbers on the bottom?
那样子摩妮卡才能加以追踪
Oh, that's so Monica can keep track.
如果有杯子不见了 她会说"27号杯在哪里"
That way, if one of them is missing, she can be like, "Where's number 27?"
你知道吗
You know what?
不 我想我不要知道
No, and I don't think I'm gonna want to.
我没办法
I can't do this.
对 所以我不想知道
Yep. Yep. That's what I didn't want to know.
对 马克 我这么做是不对的
Yeah. Oh, Mark, I'm just doing this for the wrong reasons, you know?
我只是想报复罗斯
I'm just doing it to get back at Ross.
抱歉 这对你来说不公平
I'm sorry. It's not very fair to you.
公平 天啊 你知道吗
Ah. Fair, shmair. You know?
听着 如果你想报复罗斯 我可以帮你
Look, you wanna get back at Ross, I am here for you.
真的
Really.
不 我是说我们就在这张沙发上 好好地报复他吧
No, no. I say we get back at him right here on this couch. Right here.
喔 天啊
Oh, my God.
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry about this.
没关系
That's okay.
- 你确定吗   -  对
- You sure?     - Yeah.
我可以回家自己报复他
I can just go home and get back at him by myself.
那会是21世纪的盘尼西林
And should become the penicillin of the 21 st century.
现在这家医院要迈开大步
And so today, this hospital is about to take major steps...
领导这场革命
...toward leading that revolution.
- 这真的太讽刺了   -  我能问你一件事吗
- It is truly ironic.     - Hey. Can I ask you something?
目前是什么状况
Where are we?
看到那些医生跟护士
Well, with all these doctors and nurses...
我想应该是矮人马戏团
...I'm gonna say, Midget Rodeo.
跟我说实话
Just tell me the truth.
好吧
Okay.
我想我没跟你提过这件事
Um, you know, I don't think I told you this...
我刚刚结束一段认真的恋情
...but, um, I just recently got out of a really serious relationship.
对 那不是一年前的事吗
Oh, right. Wasn't that like a year ago?
我跟你说过了
So I did tell you.
好吧 那不是问题
Okay, well, you know, that's not really the thing.
问题是我现在的生活状态是
The thing is, is that right now I'm just in a place in my life...
我只想好好做自己
...where I just need to focus on me.
- 你了解我的意思吗   -  对 我知道
- Do you know what I mean?     - Oh, yeah, I know.
- 我真的很想喜欢你   -  但你不喜欢我 好吧
- I so want to be attracted to you.     - But you're not. Okay. Good.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道吗 别那么说 这不是…
You know what? Don't be. This is not...
别那么说 真的没那么糟糕
Don't be, because it's not so bad.
- 是吗   -  对 我知道我不是琼邦•乔飞
- It's not?     - Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
或是你喜欢的那一型
Or someone you find attractive.
我只是觉得…
I just think, you know...
或许你终究会爱上我
...that you might end up feeling differently.
听着 我没有恶意
Well, look, I don't want this to come out wrong...
但我刚刚拒绝了你 你似乎还蛮有自信的
...but, uh, you seem awfully confident for a guy I just told I wasn't attracted to.
对 我超迷人的对吧
Yeah, stupidly charming, isn't it?
听着 你要吃点东西吗
Uh, listen. Let's... You wanna get something to eat?
这里让人觉得压力好大
Because this place is kind of depressing.
欢迎幕后大功臣彼特•贝克先生
Now the man who made this possible, Mr. Peter Becker.
等一下
One second.
我想这个小镇容不下我们两个
I don't think this town is big enough for the both of us to relax in.
拔枪吧
Draw.
我什么都没做
I wasn't doing anything.
她又做了什么
Uh-oh. What did she do now?
她念过耶鲁戏剧系 她就觉得她是自从有面包片以来
Just because she went to Yale Drama, she thinks she's, like, the greatest actress...
最伟大的女演员
...since sliced bread.
面包片 超棒的马克白夫人
Ah, Sliced Bread. A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
天啊 我恨她 我讨厌她说"我超有天分的"
God, I just... I hate her. I hate her with her "Oh, I'm so talented"...
"我真的好漂亮 我闻起来好香"
...and "Oh, I'm so pretty," and "Oh, I smell so good."
我想有人喜欢上某人了
I think somebody has a crush on somebody.
钱德 拜托你专心在我的问题上
Hey, Chandler, can we please try and stay focused on my problem here?
你知道吗
You know?
我是在说你 大怪胎
I'm talking about you, you big, big freak.
你疯了
Oh. You're out of your mind.
过去48小时以来 你满口都是她
Hey, you've done nothing but talk about her for the last 48 hours.
如果你还在念小学
If you were in school yard...
你会拉她的马尾 把她推倒
...you'd be pulling her pigtails and pushing her down now.
是吗 为什么我满脑子都是她
Oh, yeah? Then how come I keep thinking about her...
还有春梦呢
...in all these sexual scenarios and stuff, huh?
开心 我该那么做吗 维多 开心
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be, Vic? Happy?
你何不告诉我你想怎么做
Well, why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be, huh?
因为我就是搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out.
我跟你说话 你没反应
I talk to you, and it's nothing.
你看着我 完全没反应
You look at me, and nothing.
就是没反应
Nothing.
你们让我想飞上天
You guys make me fly.
飞很高
High.
好吧 明天从这里接下去
Okay, we're gonna pick it up here tomorrow.
- 那是…   -  好多了
- Well, that was, uh...     - Better?
对 那真的是…
Yeah, yeah, it was definitely...
一大进步
...an improvement.
- 晚安   -  凯特
- Good night.     - Uh, Kate.
什么事
Yeah?
你忘了穿鞋
You, uh... You forgot your shoes.
或许我需要鞋子 对吧
I'm probably gonna need those, huh?
- 好吧   -  听着
- Okay.     - Hey, listen...
要一起喝杯咖啡吗
...you, uh, feel like getting a cup of coffee?
- 凯特   -  什么
- Um... Yo.     - Kate.
- 准备要走了吗   -  对
- You ready to go?     - Yeah.
非常好
Very nice. Very nice.
那就…
So, um...
- 明天见   -  当然
- See you tomorrow, huh?     - Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
- 对   -  晚安
- Right.     - Good night.
嘿
Hey.
（"苹果世界"）
为什么不是"蜘蛛人"
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
譬如葛德曼或席佛曼
You know, like Goldman, Silverman?
因为那不是他的姓氏
Because it's not his last name.
- 真的   -  没错 他又不是…
- It isn't?     - No, it's not, like...
菲尔•史派德曼
Like Phil Spiderman.
他是变身为蜘殊的…
He's a spider...
人
...man.
葛德曼是姓氏
You know, like, uh... Like Goldman is a last name.
可是根本就没有金人
But there's no gold man.
好吧
Oh, okay.
应该有金人的
There should be a Gold Man.
- 嗨   -  嘿 瑞秋
- Hey.     - Hey, Rach.
- 工作还顺利吧   -  太棒了
- How was work?     - Oh, great.
虽然我一屁股坐下 发现根本没有椅子
Although I did sit down where there wasn't a chair.
对了 罗斯把你的东西拿过来
By the way, Ross dropped by a box of your stuff.
我早就知道他会那么做
Oh. Well, I guess I had that one coming.
我要把它拿去丢了 或许只是一堆洗发精跟…
I'm just gonna throw it out. It's probably just a bunch of shampoo and...
怎么了
Something wrong?
不 没事
Hmm. No. Nothing.
金人有什么样的力量
So, uh, what kind of powers would Gold Man have?
好吧 他能点石成金
Okay. Well, he would turn things to gold.
- 如果那本来就是黄金呢   -  他就完成了他的使命
- What about things that are already gold?     - Ah. His work is done.
好吧 来玩我的游戏
Okay, let's play my game.
好的
Okay.
好吧 你这个王八蛋
All right, you yellow-bellied, lily-livered...
拔枪吧
Draw.
对 这真的很好玩
Yeah, it's fun.